What if I told you that you could eat an
entire pint of ice cream every single
day and still stay on track of your
fitness goals? That's exactly what the
Ninja Cream allows you to do. Let me
show you the five flavors I made this
week. This first one is an Oreo
McFlurry. One of my all-time favorite
recipes. It honestly tastes as good as a
real McDonald's McFlurry. Then I wanted
to get into the holiday spirit. I made
this eggnog flavor and it was just
insanely rich and creamy. One of my
favorite flavors I've done in a while.
Then I had to run back one of my
childhood favorites, cosmic brownie.
This is a brownie batter base topped
with those little rainbow chocolate
sprinkles. It hits every single time.
Then I finally decided to hop on the
Dubai chocolate trend. This was a
pistachio base, probably the best
pistachio base you'll find on social
media. Topped with some katayifi and
melted chocolate. Dairy Queen just came
out with their winter blizzard flavors,
so I decided to recreate them in the
Ninja Creamy. This was a vanilla base
with protein frosting mixed in and then
topped with protein cookie dough bites
and some festive sprinkles.